

CONTACT

- +91 (889)-121-8009
- +91 (890)-755-2606
- 11/1980, Harisree, Panchayath Raj Road, Palluruthy PO, Cochin-682006
- in linkedin.com/nidhinharilal
- nidd.odoo.com

LANGUAGES

English
Spanish
Malayalam
Russian

Hindi

SKILLS

- · SEO, SMM, SEM
- · Advertising & Branding
- · Wordpress, CMS, HTML, Script
- Business Enhancement Strategies
- Team Leadership & Management
- E-Business, Creative Design
- Presentation & Consulting
- Adobe Suite, Davinci Resolve
- Web Development

INTERESTS

- Digital Marketing Trends
- Technology Trends & Al
- Content Creation
- Tech Innovations
- Art & Music
- Travel

NIDHIN HARILAL

THE DIGITAL EXPERT

PROFILE SUMMARY

A well experienced digital marketing professional having worked in sectors not limited to Sales, Airlines, Retail, Digital Marketing and Business Consultation, E-Commerce. An artist and a creative person discovering creativity in everything and having a desire and zest for building and maintaining professional relationships

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Digital Marketing Manager | Trusttech Solutions, IN | 2024-Present

- Team Management
- Complete Digital Marketing (SEO, SEM, SMM) & Branding
- Desing-DM team combined tasks and brand promotions
- Technical coding and software setup and market analysis
- Backend web & Content management
- Serving as technical partner/client of brand Trust Capital (Cyprus, Seychelles, UAE)

Digital Marketing Manager | AGES Learning Solutions, USA | 2022 – 2023

- Developed and executed comprehensive digital media strategies resulting in a 30% increase in organic reach and a 50% boost in website traffic within six months and enhanced social media presence and handled e-commerce platforms and marketing
- Managed multiple brands out of which two are US based and one is Indian based and lead generation of valid 500+ for recruitment alone
- Implemented more digital presence and recruitment visibility by constant communication

Digital Marketing Manager AVA Cholayil Healthcare, IN | 2021–2022

- Produced and curated engaging content across multiple platforms, increasing social media followers by 20% and driving 50% more website conversions.
- Conducted in-depth market research and competitor analysis to identify trends and opportunities for content creation. Implemented influencer partnerships, resulting in a 15% increase in revenue and handled e-commerce platforms
- Done campaigns that resulted in 6 Cr+ business in a span of 8 months and produced 21k+ leads. Handled budget of up to 72 lacs and monthly up to 8 lacs.

Digital Marketing Captain | Blusteak Media, IN | 2021

- Produced and created engaging content across multiple platforms and did blogging
- Handled multiple clients and communication
- Conducted in-depth market research and competitor analysis to identify trends and opportunities for content creation. Implemented influencer partnerships and
- Co-developed a Chat based AI platform for lead generation based on WATI and managed a team of content writers, video editors, graphic designers and SEO professionals.

Senior Digital Marketing Consultant & Trainer | Freelance, IN2020-Present

E-Commerce Exécutive | North Tours LLC, DXB, UAE | 2013-2014

SEO Analyst & Digital Marketing Trainer | AvivDigital | 2018-2019

Assistant Buyer | Lulu Group International | 2019

Senior Sales Executive | Imagine [APR] | 2015-2016

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration (MBA), E-Business

Annamalai University, IN | 2015 – 2017

Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA)

M.G University,IN | 2009–2012